smile.co.uk 2016-03-16

# cookie policy

The privacy of customers is very important to us, and how we deal with personal information is outlined in our terms and conditions. We hope the way in which we gather and use your personal information addresses and respects any concerns you may have.

For full details of how your information may be used for credit reference and fraud prevention purposes by The Co-operative Bank and the Credit Reference Agencies please read our guide on personal data.

## **we will only use the personal information we gather:**

  * in the normal course of our business to provide the products and services you have requested
  * to identify you when you contact us
  * to determine if we can offer you a better service or more relevant products
  * to send you e-mail updates of service changes which are important to you or which we feel may be of interest to you
  * for credit assessment, to review the conduct of and to administer/operate your accounts
  * for statistical analysis, including automated techniques (eg behaviour and credit scoring) and to monitor and analyse our business

## **we will disclose your personal information only to:  
**

  * our agents and sub-contractors to administer and operate your account or to conduct our business
  * the insurer of any payment or card protection cover which you take out in connection with your account
  * our licensed credit reference agency who may keep a record of any search we make and your personal information may be shared with and used by other lenders in assessing applications from you or members of your household
  * any person to whom we transfer our rights or obligations under this agreement
  * for debt tracing or fraud prevention
  * to help desk advisers, minicom/typetalk operators or their equivalent
  * if required or compelled to do so by law
